installation
============

[Contenu de l'installation]

Introduction
------------
This section explains how to install the django_insta application on your system.

Prerequisites
-------------
Before starting the installation, make sure you have the following:
- Python 3.x
- Django 3.x
- Other Python libraries (if applicable)

Installation
------------
To install the django_insta application, follow the steps below:

1. Clone the repository from GitHub:
   https://github.com/celiaq/catsapp

2. Navigate to the project directory:
